I'll call it over to the regular schedule meeting my city council for Tuesday April 21st, 2026. We got
We're just skip the three. We're gonna move the
public input to the end
3a claims list
3b minutes from the April 7th 2026 regular meeting
3c doesn't a Todd Barnes to be the authorized agent for the okay MF MRF retirement plan Cindy
So as you know at this point, I'm going to retire here in just a couple of weeks and I am currently the
authorized agent for our city employee plan and so I need to pass the hat to Todd Barnes to be our
Designated authorized agent what that person does is make sure that all of the enrollment forms get sent in
Everything gets processed
And nothing changes. So as you are the governing body for our retirement plan
I need you to authorize it and there you'll need to sign the document
Congratulations on your time. We're gonna miss you though
Item four other new business if any which the residents is the posting this agenda five staff report
six mayor council community announcements
seven city manager communications
Eight this meeting will now be continued from council chambers read to me in the staff room for the purpose of executive session
Oh, wait, sorry. Hold on. I moved the public comment to the end. So we're gonna back up before we do that
Oh after executive, okay
I want to make a motion to come out of executive session. I think you just kind of declare
Just declare this out
Alright declare side of executive session at 709. I'd like to make a motion that we table the items discuss an executive session tonight
No
And
The names Rick Aldridge
Concerned citizen reason. I'm here this evening
I think we all know and understand the issues that have been going on here. That's been centered around our mayor
I've only been here 17 years and most of that's been under the I'll say tutelage of mayor bless Parker
We met quite a few years ago pre kovat. We were kovat together
And we can bite each other every now and then he's been a strong supporter of what I do
Which is taking care of people on the street
He continues to provide
me with with the
Access to be able to use facilities that we need to do that to make sure we can help people
He is an absolute
Superstar when it comes to the people in this city
Like any city you're going to have people that disagree
But we have had so much success in this city because of this man and I'll debate with anybody on that
Roads are an issue roads are an issue everywhere in this country
But you take a look what bless has brought to this city in the last couple years
I'm just I'm a little bit frustrated that we have to do this because of some
things that are being said and done, but I just want to make sure that everybody knows that
And everybody does know it's in this room tonight
I don't think anybody in here is going to speak negatively, but bless has brought nothing but but prestige to this city
We're talked about in Oklahoma City. We're talked about by our elected officials in Oklahoma City. We're talked about other states
They see what we do. They see what bless does
They come to bless and go. How do you do it?
And that man loves this city
There's not a person around that has loved that city that's held his position for this long
And I just can't stand the fact that this stuff is being dragged through the mud the way it is
And people need to be ashamed of themselves and I doubt
Seriously that most of the people in this city can go without any a plum blemish mark on their background
Or their morality or anything like that and just because it's our mayor doesn't mean anything
Okay, he's a man. He's a family man, and he's a leader of this city
And it's just disgusting that people want to find something out and want to drag it through the mud the way they do
And I challenge anybody to open up their damn closet, and we'll talk about what's in y'all's closet
I'll talk about what's in my closet. I don't have a problem with that
But to do this and to damage the family if the way they're doing it is just sickening
And that's just for bless in this other item that's on here tonight. It's absolutely disgusting again
Give me a break people
Honestly everything that goes on in this country, and we're sitting here worried about some of these things that are going on in our little city
Look at the bright side of what we've done in this city look at the people what they've done
And we're sitting here looking at putting people through a microscope. I'll put everybody put me through a microscope. I could care less
And I you'll find stuff who cares
But the bottom line is this is not the way it should be done, and it's disgusting
It's called journalism. It's not called journalism
And I wish Mike Woodruff was here tonight so I could applaud that man for what he did today
That is journalism not this punk crap. That's going on that people want to get clicks and get paid for that's all it's about
Click my page so I can get all the money in the world
Thank you, Rick
Next up you have David Davis. Hi council. Thank you for letting me speak
Not counting my time in college in a short stint in Springfield, Missouri
I've been in this town for 56 years and 27 days
Miami a town that until February of 1986 had a tremendous employer. We all knew as BF Goodrich
bless happens to be two years two days older than I am and
Those were dark days
There's been 25 to 30 years worth of dark days following that period
Bless Parker has spent more time
effort thankless hours
Promoting the causes of Miami than any mayor. I've had the work the opportunity to work with I
joined the council in 2019 and got to work with Rudy until
Bless was elected in 2020
Bless loves, Miami
He shows it with his actions every time he has an opportunity
For people to take bless on that he's corrupt or underhanded
Proves they don't know bless
Bless has an opinion and won't hesitate to share it with you good or bad
He's hurt my feelings before he's made me laugh before because he didn't tell me what I wanted to hear
If he's done one video promoting our businesses citizens youth
Homebuilders he's done hundreds
No one in my lifetime has worked harder to promote the city of Miami, Oklahoma
It sickens me to have people with
Little to no goal except to create doubt discontent and be able to potentially stir up people against the one warrior bless
That has been the face of our community and the heart and effort behind it. We haven't been in such a good place as we are
right now
Dismissing this crap show, but I don't want to take anything from Darryl
We haven't been here in a long time there's developers calling me I run a real estate firm here in town
There's developers calling me stock and talking about beginning new developments. There's businesses coming to town
there's more restaurant variety here than there's been in 40 years and
We have some people around in our in our town that want to see it fail
And that is really sad and unfortunate. Of course negative news
spreads fast
Especially AI doctored news this witch hunt cramp needs to which hunt crap needs to start
And we need to support this man
my friend
Next Billy Forbes. I'm not I'm not very good at this, but
I'll let y'all know that a lot of you may know me and I've got one a pretty
Past I just recently have gone to a federal court to work on some charges on me and
Bless is written a letter on my behalf along with the many people in this community
If it wasn't for bless, I wouldn't be standing here right now
Like Rick I work with people I work with trying to improve people's lives and blesses helped me all the way through this
I mean I started a sober living home here that has grown
We've caused a ripple effect that that's gone all the way
And you know if it hadn't been for people like bless, I'm speaking to bless
As blessed as a human. I've got a lot of dirt on me. You can more than welcome to dig up anything on me
Please do and you might forget to find something I forgot about
Because I'm not I'm not I mean I want I want to get my life straightened out
You know, it's people like this community
that has helped me, you know straighten my life up and I'm just trying to get back to
Community the best I can and without blesses help. Like I said, I wouldn't be here today
He wrote he wrote good words on my behalf along with several people in this community
You know, that's
Don't listen to everything
Because you know things get things get turned around
Be your own character
Judge character. Don't let somebody influence your thoughts
God bless you all. Thank you
Thank Billy
Next is Darryl Taylor. My name is Darryl Taylor and I've lived here in July will be 67 years
I've known blessed for about the past 40 of those years and
As a child I remember there was a pretty good mayor named Wayne pack
he was instrumental a lot of things that
Happened around here and he had a big
Mansion like house out on the hill south of the fairgrounds
but I'll tell you kind of God blesses like one day I had a
Thought that I would try to get people through Facebook to volunteer for some trash cleanup
I noticed a area in my neighborhood. That was pretty bad shape
So I called bless and I told him I said I'm gonna put this on Facebook and I'd like for you to come
well about 15 or 20 minutes later, he was there and
we picked up a lot of trash that day and
With the help of bless and the city of Miami
The NEO wrestlers volunteered from for me one day. I had 36 wrestlers and
I
Had the city
They put up signs to warn people that there was workers out and stuff
They also put a trailer in the parking lot of the softball park
Where we deposited all the trash because we were interested in seeing how much we got
That one day one afternoon actually
we got twelve thousand five hundred pounds of trash off the streets of Miami and
There's been several times that
I hung out with bless one afternoon to take up toys for underprivileged children and
We collected about ten thousand dollars worth of toys in that afternoon at the Walmart parking lot
I just don't think anybody works harder for Miami than bless does and I'm sure glad I don't have that job
Because I don't think I'd put that much effort into it, but I'm sure glad that bless does that's all I got to say
Next is Corey stops
I'm here tonight to raise a serious concern prior to any consideration in regards this city attorney's
contract for renewal this evening
I've attained a team documentation showing the information related to a minor child's accident was shared outside of appropriate channels and
Subsequently appeared publicly publicly in a manner that is both inaccurate and harmful
This includes the use of the child's name and false claims associated with the incident
Additionally the publicly shared material appears to identify the source of that information
Which would be Misty Barnes?
given the seriousness of this matter including the involvement of a minor and
The potential misuse of confidential and privileged information
I believe it warrants careful review before any decisions are made regarding continued representation of this city
I am not requesting immediate
conclusions, but I'm asking that this issue be acknowledged and
Appropriately considered prior to contract action. I'm prepared to provide you documentation for every thing that I assert tonight
I appreciate your time and consideration in this matter. Thank you
13 motion to adjourn